CONTACT

- 9961699106
- ajithpg2411@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/ajith-pg
- Kerala,India

AJITH PG

Front End Developer

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Science APJ Abdul Kalam Technological university 2015 - 2019

SKILLS

JS Framework:

React JS, Next JS

Web Technologies :

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery

CSS Framework

SASS, Tailwind CSS, Material UI

Tools

Git Version Control
VS Code Editor

Design Tools

Figma

Adobe XD

ABOUT ME

Passionate Front-end web developer with 3+ years of experience in Web Developemnt uisng React, JavaScript, Jquery, HTML5, and CSS to build all aspects of the user experience and user interface for Websites, CMS Sites and e-commerce sites.

WORK EXPERIENCE

O Jan 2021- Present Tata Consultancy Services(TCS)

Javascript Developer

- Implementing new client Requirements for Bank Trading Application
- Developing UI related Changes for the Application

June 2020 - April 2021 GL InfoTech,Thrissur

React Developer

- Implemented new features and User interfaces in collaboration with clients and project team.
- Converting UI Design from scratch for Ecommerce and CMS Sites using HTML,CSS,Javascript
- Resolved browsers compatibility issues, Improving Website performance and SEO Rankings.

O Dec 2019 - May 2020 i-Techtonic System,Coimbatore

Web Developer

- Design and Develop user interface for Websites
- Built web pages that are more user-interactive using Javascript,jQuery and Bootstrap.